Lloyd E. Cotsen collection of Potter Family photographs,1865-1935: Finding Aid
Cotsen Children's Library
- Portraits, 1865-1935; 276 items
  - Beatrix with Blanche and Kate Potter, at Bush Hall, 1884 August 29; 138; 1 item 16.4 x 19.9 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 29/ 84. Rupert Potter's stamp:photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Kate + Blanche Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: with Beatrix. Print from same negative found in Marseille-Genoa-Pisa album, 15r. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 139.
    Catalog number: 350
  - Beatrix with Blanche and Kate Potter, at Bush Hall, 1884 August 29; 139; 1 item 16.6 x 21.0 cm.
    Title supplied by catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 29/84. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: B. Kate + Blanche Potter. Photographs from same sitting: Marseilles-Genoa-Pisa album, 15r; CTSN Potter 138. Torn.
    Catalog number: 351
  - Mrs. Potter, Clara Potter, and Ethel Leech in landaulette, with coachman and Beatrix, Holehird, 1889 August; 140; 1 item 10.3 x 19.9 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Mounted to 12.9 x 22.8 cm. board. Mount inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Holehird/ Aug 1889. Print from same negative found in Marseille-Genoa-Pisa album, 22r.
    Catalog number: 352
  - Clara and Rupert Potter, circa 1865; 141; 1 item 11.9 x 16.6 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Clara + Rupert Potter. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 142-144.
    Catalog number: 356
  - Mrs. Potter and Clara Potter, circa 1865; 142; 1 item 12.0 x 17.0 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Mrs Potter + Clara?. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 141. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 143-144.
    Catalog number: 357
  - Mrs. Potter and Clara Potter, circa 1865; 143; 1 item 12.1 x 16.7 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Helen + Clara Potter. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 141. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 142, 144.
    Catalog number: 358
  - Mrs. Potter and Clara Potter, circa 1865; 144; 1 item 11.3 x 15.9 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Clara Potter/ Helen. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 141. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 142-143. Glue applied to back of print.
    Catalog number: 359
  - Rupert Potter, Clara Potter, and Mrs. Potter, at Lingholm, 1888 September; 145; 1 item 16.9 x 21.4 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm/ Sep. 1888. Rupert Potter's stamp:photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Rupert Helen [ampersand] Clara Potter.
    Catalog number: 360
  - Mrs Potter with two female relations[?], in open car with chauffeur (probably David Beckett), 1908 August 9; 146; 1 item 12.1 x 16.4
    Photographed during Stock Park stay. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 9 1908/ o l Sp d [sh]/ R Potter. [Have used title from catalog, though none of these women resembles Mrs. Potter--CW]
    Catalog number: 361
  - Edmund Potter and Professor J.C. Wilson, 1883; 147; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed at Camfield Place. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mr Edmund Potter/ JC. Wilson/ Camfield Place/ 1883/ R Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Camfield Place/ belonged to old Mrs. Potter; grandmother of Beatrix Potter and now is the home of Barbara Cartland.
    Catalog number: 362
  - Rupert Potter, Mr. Gaskell, Jane Leech, Mrs Potter, and Grandmamma Leech, circa 1870; 148; 1 item 11.5 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed in doorway at Dalguise. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke?: Dalguise. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Potters with Rev [ampersand] Mrs Gaskell.
    Catalog number: 363
  - Rupert Potter, Mrs. Potter, Jane Leech, and Mr. Gaskell, circa 1870; 149; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Rupert Helen/ and Mrs Gaskell (Cranford)/ [ampersand] Rev Gaskell.
    Catalog number: 364
  - Mr. Gaskell, Mrs. Potter, and Edmund Potter, circa 1875; 150; 1 item 11.0 x 14.6 cm.
    Photographed on the porch at Dalguise House. Title supplied from catalog. Mounted to 11.0 x 14.6 cm. board. Mount inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Aunt Helen/ with Mr. Gaskell. Torn, partially detached from mount.
    Catalog number: 366
  - Rupert Potter and Mr. Gaskell, circa 1875; 151; 1 item 22.0 x 16.7 cm.
    Photographed on grounds of Dalguise House. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Dalguise/ Rupert + Wm Gaskell.
    Catalog number: 367
  - Mrs. Potter, Grandmamma Leech(?), the painter John Brett(?), and Jane Leech(?), in the doorway at Dalguise, circa 1870; 152; 1 item 10.2 x 15.6 cm.
    Photographed on the porch at Dalguise House. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in ballpoint by Stephanie Duke?: Aunt Helen/ + Clara Potter/ with John Brett/ [ampersand] Ms Brett. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: (painter). Glue applied to back of print.
    Catalog number: 375
  - Clara Potter, sister of Rupert, circa 1865; 153; 1 item 13.7 x 9.9 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Beatrix Potter: Aunt Clara Potter.
    Catalog number: 379
  - Mrs. (Mary) Crompton Potter, wife of Edmund Crompton Potter, circa 1870; 154; 1 item 16.0 x 11.8 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Beatrix Potter: Mrs Crompton Potter.
    Catalog number: 380
  - Jessie Potter, circa 1870; 155; 1 item 11.8 x 8.8 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. No inscriptions. Photographs from same sitting: Marseilles-Genoa-Pisa album, 6r; CTSN Potter 127.
    Catalog number: 381
  - Kate Potter, seen in profile, 1882 May 25; 156; 1 item 16.1 x 11.2 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Kate Potter/ R Potter/ May 25 1882/ a/ [B]. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 157.
    Catalog number: 382
  - Kate Potter, three-quarter length portrait, 1882 May 25; 157; 1 item 16.2 x 11.2 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: May 25 1882/ a/ [B]. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Kate Potter. Large portion of print missing, lower left corner. Photographs from same sitting: CTSN Potter 156.
    Catalog number: 383
  - Kate Potter in profile, wearing checked dress, 1882; 158; 1 item 15.8 x 11.4 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Rupert Potter's stamp: photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1882. Inscribed in ballpoint by Stephanie Duke?: Kate Potter.
    Catalog number: 384
  - Kate Potter wearing paisley dress, 1886 August 29; 159; 1 item 18.4 x 11.5 cm.
    Photographed at Bush Hall. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Kate Potter/ Aug 29/86/ R Potter.
    Catalog number: 385
  - Jane Leech, circa 1875; 160; 1 item 12.1 x 9.4 cm.
    Photographed on the porch at Dalguise House. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Jane Leech/ R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 161.
    Catalog number: 388
  - Jane Leech, circa 1875; 161; 1 item 10.8 x 8.2 cm.
    Photographed on the porch at Dalguise House. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Stephanie Duke?: Jane Leech. Printed with oval mask. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 160.
    Catalog number: 389
  - Young male realtion: William leech?, undated; 162; 1 item 10.4 x 7.8 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in ink, unknown hand: ? Uncle William Leech.
    Catalog number: 390
  - Young male realtion: William leech?, undated; 163; 1 item 11.7 x 7.8 cm.
    Title supplied by catalog. Inscribed in ink, unknown hand: ? Uncle W. Leech.
    Catalog number: 391
  - Cousin Mary Harrison, daughter of Aunt Mary Harrison, undated; 164; 1 item 12.0 x 8.9 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Beatrix Potter: Cousin Mary Harrison.
    Catalog number: 392
  - Small boy and elderly woman (Grandmamma Leech?) in a garden, undated; 165; 1 item 17.8 x 10.9
    Title supplied from catalog. Portion of date inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, illegible.
    Catalog number: 393
  - Charles Wrigley(?) and his mother Aunt Polly Wrigley, nee Potter, circa 1880; 166; 1 item 17.5 x 21.8 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. No inscription. Corner folded.
    Catalog number: 394
  - Charles and Blanche Wrigley, with baby and dog, 1887 June; 167; 1 item 14.7 x 9.4 cm.
    Photographed at Helm Island? Title supplied from catalog. Mounted to 16.6 x 10.9 cm. board. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Mr + Mrs C Wrigley/ [Helm] Island// June 1887/ M. Wrigley.
    Catalog number: 395
  - Mrs. Bruce and Mrs. Wrigley in open car with chauffeur, 1911 August 16; 168; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed at Lindeth How. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 16 1911/ Mrs Bruce Mrs Wrigley/ R Potter. Corner folded.
    Catalog number: 397
  - Young woman, seated, undated; 169; 1 item 11.0 x 13.4 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Two portraits untrimmed on single sheet. Corners folded.
    Catalog number: 398
  - Young woman: Ethel Leech?, undated; 170; 1 item 12.8 x 8.7 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. No inscription.
    Catalog number: 399
  - Girl with a parasol, undated; 171; 1 item 16.6 x 12.0 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Possibly a cousin? No inscription.
    Catalog number: 400
  - Two young women seated at a small table; possibly Leech cousins?, undated; 172; 1 item 11.2 x 14.6 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Rupert Potter's stamp: photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Corner folded.
    Catalog number: 401
  - Two seated women, undated; 173; 1 item 11.0 x 11.2 cm.
    Catalog number: 402
  - Young man; possibly Leech cousin?, undated; 174; 1 item 11.9 x 13.4 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Two portraits untrimmed on single sheet. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 175. Same subject, or brother, of young man pictured in CTSN Potter 175?
    Catalog number: 403
  - Young man; possibly Leech cousin?, undated; 175; 1 item 11.3 x 13.1 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Two portraits untrimmed on single sheet. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 174. Same subject, or brother, of young man pictured in CTSN Potter 174?
    Catalog number: 404
  - Young woman and young girl, embracing, 1885 May; 176; 1 item 19.0 x 11.8 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Mounted to 20.9 x 12.8 cm. cabinet card. Lower margin of mount stamped, recto: H.S. Mendelssohn./ 27, Cathcart Road,/ South Kensington, S.W. Verso of mount inscribed in ink by Rupert Potter: May. 1885. Verso of mount inscribed in ink, unknown period hand: 5231.
    Catalog number: 405
  - Three women, possibly Leech cousins, and a man, circa 1885; 177; 1 item 9.3 x 18.6 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription.
    Catalog number: 406
  - John Bright, at Lingholm, 1885 September 11; 178; 1 item 17.7 x 22.6 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 11/85. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Bright?/ Lingholm. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: John Bright, M.P. Corners folded.
    Catalog number: 407
  - John Bright, at Lingholm, 1885 September 11; 179; 1 item 16.7 x 11.5 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 11/85. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Bright? Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: John Bright/ M.P./ ([brought]/ in the/ repeal of/ the Corn Laws./ Act.).
    Catalog number: 408
  - Mrs. Creighton, 1884 June 24; 180; 1 item 22.9 x 17.4 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mrs. Creighton/ R Potter/ June 24/84. Corners folded. Torn.
    Catalog number: 409
  - William Gaskell, reading, circa 1875; 181; 1 item 13.0 x 8.5 cm.
    Photographed in the doorway at Dalguise House? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Mr. Gaskell. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: (husband of/ Mrs Gaskell/ author of Cranford). Printed with oval mask. Corners folded.
    Catalog number: 410
  - William Gaskell,at Dalguise, circa 1875; 182; 1 item 11.9 x 9.4 cm.
    Photographed in the doorway at Dalguise House. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Rev. W. Gaskell/ R Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Husband of/ Mrs Gaskell who/ wrote (Cranford).
    Catalog number: 411
  - William Gaskell holding book, at Dalguise, circa 1880; 183; 1 item 12.7 x 9.1 cm.
    Photographed in the doorway at Dalguise House. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Mr Gaskell. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 1880.
    Catalog number: 412
  - Lillie Langtry at Eastwood, Dunkeld, 1879; 184; 1 item 10.8 x 8.2 cm.
    Photographed at Eastwood? Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mrs Langtry// 1879. Rupert Potter's stamp:photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Printed with oval mask. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 186.
    Catalog number: 414
  - Sir Louis Mallet, at Camfield Place, 1882 January 23; 185; 1 item 21.1 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed at Camfield Place. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: The Rt Hon Sir Louis Mallet CB/ Camfield Place// Jan 23 1882/ [h]/ [11]. Rupert Potter's stamp:photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Camfield Place was owned by/ Beatrix Potters grandparents. Now/ owned by Barbara Cartland.
    Catalog number: 415
  - Sir John Everett Millais and Lillie Langtry, at Eastwood, 1879; 186; 1 item 16.0 x 19.1 cm.
    Photographed at Eastwood, Dunkeld. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1879/ Copyright. Rupert Potter's stamp twice:copyright./ photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in Ballpoint, unknown hand: Lily Langtree/ [ampersand] Millais who painted her. Portions of emulsion missing. Patches of paper glued to surface of print. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 184.
    Catalog number: 416
  - Sir John Everett Millais in later life, undated; 187; 1 item 12.6 x 10.3 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Millais/ (painter).
    Catalog number: 417
  - Mrs Millais, later Lady Millais, undated; 188; 1 item 12.6 x 8.3 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Mrs Millais.
    Catalog number: 418
  - Lady Millais in profile, 1890 September; 189; 1 item 12.5 x 10.2 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep/ 1890. Rupert Potter's stamp:photographed by/ Rupert Potter. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Mrs Millais. Printed with oval mask.
    Catalog number: 419
  - Caroline Millais at an open window, 1875 July; 190; 1 item 16.0 x 10.9 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Mounted to 16.0 x 10.9 cm. card. Verso of mount inscribed in ink by Rupert Potter: R Potter photo. July 1875 Bolton Gardens. Printed with oval mask.
    Catalog number: 420
  - Caroline Millais(?), double portrait, undated; 191; 1 item 14.8 x 10.3 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Printed with oval mask.
    Catalog number: 421
  - Mary Millais, at Eastwood, Dunkeld, 1880 September 13; 192; 1 item 18.4 x 12.4 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter?: [Stu] Sep. 13. 1880.
    Catalog number: 422
  - Mabel Ogden, in front of door at Wray Castle, 1882 August 30; 193; 1 item 15.6 x 10.8 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mabel Ogden/ Wray Castle/ R Potter/ Aug 30/82/ [b].
    Catalog number: 423
  - The Rawnsleys, with two others, 1903 September 16; 194; 1 item 16.4 x 21.2 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 16 1903/ R Potter. Corners folded. Torn.
    Catalog number: 424
  - 'Red Riding Hood': young girl with a basket, climbing stile, circa 1894; 195; 1 item 16.4 x 12.1 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. The girl is a sister of Partons boy, who Beatrix sketched for the Tailor of Gloucestershire. According to catalog, Beatrix used this photograph as an aid for one of her Red Riding Hood designs, dated August 1894 (see drawings in the Free Library of Philadelphia Collection: front view, FLP 45; back view FLP 43).
    Catalog number: 425
  - Baby (a Postelthwaite?) with toy, undated; 196; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Title supplied by catalog. No inscription. Possibly photographed by Beatrix? Same sitting as CTSN Potter 197.
    Catalog number: 426
  - Baby (a Postelthwaite?) with toy, undated; 197; 1 item 10.8 x 8.2 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Possibly photographed by Beatrix? Same sitting as CTSN Potter 196.
    Catalog number: 427
  - Little girl (a Postlethwaite?) in a frilled bonnet, with cats, undated; 198; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Possibly photographed by Beatrix? Same sitting as CTSN Potter 199.
    Catalog number: 428
  - Little girl (a Postlethwaite?) in a frilled bonnet, with cats, undated; 199; 1 item 12.0 x 8.3 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Possibly photographed by Beatrix? Same sitting as CTSN Potter 198.
    Catalog number: 429
  - Little girl (a Rogerson?) in a rocking chair, with dog, undated; 200; 1 item 10.7 x 15.1 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke: Lakefield Cottage. Possibly photographed by Beatrix?
    Catalog number: 430
  - Portrait of a woman, undated; 201; 1 item 7.1 x 5.8 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Mounted to paper, 7.5 x 6.2 cm; paper mounted to deckle-edge card, 18.9 x 12.2 cm. Inscribed in ink, recto of mount: Nod. Schlemmer/ Montreux.
    Catalog number: 432
  - Organ grinder and monkey, 1879; 202; 1 item 11.9 x 7.6 cm.
    Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter?: 1879.
    Catalog number: 433
  - The Potters' domestic staff at Holehird, circa 1889; 203; 1 item 11.1 x 15.2 cm.
    Title supplied by catalog. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke?: Holehird Staff? Inscribed in ballpoint by Stephanie Duke: Domestic staff of the Potter/ family/ at Holehird.
    Catalog number: 434
  - One of the 'Pace Eggers'(?), standing outside Hill Top, 1912; 204; 1 item 16.5 x 12.3 cm.
    Photographed by Rupert Potter or Beatrix Potter? Title supplied from catalog. No inscription. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 205. Pace Egging was a regional Easter costume tradition.
    Catalog number: 435
  - One of the 'Pace Eggers'(?), seated outside Hill Top, 1912; 205; 1 item 12.2 x 8.6 cm.
    Photographed by Rupert Potter or Beatrix Potter? Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Same sitting as CTSN Potter 204. Pace Egging was a regional Easter costume tradition.
    Catalog number: 436
  - Peacock and peahen on a garden bench, 1891 October; 206; 1 item 11.8 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed at Bedwell Lodge [according to catalog]. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Oct 1891.
    Catalog number: 438
  - Poultry at Bedwell Lodge, 1891; 207; 1 item 11.0 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed at Bedwell Lodge [according to catalog]. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter?: HBP 1891.
    Catalog number: 439
  - Farmyard ducks in their run at Hill Top, 1911 August 17; 208; 1 item 8.3 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed at Hill Top, Sawrey. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 17 1911/ Sawrey/ R Potter. [note: The dimensions of this photograph do not match those given in the catalog. However, given the inscription and subject, which no other photograph matches, probably is photograph refered to as cat.440]
    Catalog number: 440
  - Four ducks, undated; 209; 1 item 8.6 x 13.8 cm.
    Catalog number: 441
  - Young cat on window sill, with plant pots, undated; 210; 1 item 10.7 x 15.6
    Title supplied from catalog. Mounted to 14.4 x 23.1 cm. card. No inscription.
    Catalog number: 442
  - Kitten in a basket, held by Beatrix(?), undated; 211; 1 item 11.3 x 15.3 cm.
    Catalog number: 443
  - Cattle on a hillside, undated; 212; 1 item 5.7 x 8.7 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Printed on Selo paper.
    Catalog number: 444
  - Cattle in a field, undated; 213; 1 item 5.7 x 8.7 cm.
  - Cattle in a field, undated; 214; 1 item 5.7 x 8.7 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 94. Printed on Selo paper.
  - Cattle at Troutbeck Park, undated; 215; 1 item 9.6 x 11.9 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke?: Troutbeck Park. Printed on Velox paper.
    Catalog number: 497
  - Cattle at Troutbeck Park, undated; 216; 1 item 9.6 x 11.9 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by John Duke?: Troutbeck Park? Printed on Velox paper.
  - Cattle at Troutbeck Park, undated; 217; 1 item 9.5 x 12.0 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Printed on Velox paper.
  - Cattle at Troutbeck Park, undated; 218; 1 item 9.5 x 12.0 cm.
  - Ayrshire cow, facing right, undated; 219; 1 item 8.0 x 10.7 cm.
  - Cow facing left, held by two boys, undated; 220; 1 item 9.6 x 12.1 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 1035.
  - Cow facing right, held by a man, undated; 221; 1 item 11.2 x 15.6 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscriptions.
  - Cow facing right, in a field, undated; 222; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Catalog number: 444?
  - Two cows, in a barnyard, undated; 223; 1 item 11.4 x 15.6 cm.
  - Dachsund in collar; Benjamin Bouncer climbing doorstep. [dog and rabbit], undated; 224; 1 item 12.7 x 10.0 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. Two prints mounted to 14.4 x 23.1 cm. card. Both printed with oval mask. No inscription.
    Catalog number: 445, 457
  - Black curly-coated dog with trimmed claws, undated; 225; 1 item 11.6 x 9.3 cm.
    Catalog number: 446
  - Kep, Beatrix Potter's collie dog, at Hill Top, circa 1913; 226; 1 item 12.0 x 16.2 cm.
    Photographed at Hill Top. Title supplied from catalog. Inscribed in ballpoint by Stephanie Duke?: Beatrix Potter's sheep dog. Inscribed in pencil by unknown hand: Kep.
    Catalog number: 447
  - Donkey and cart, with small boy, undated; 227; 1 item 11.2 x 15.6 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Corners folded.
    Catalog number: 448
  - White pony and cart, held by Robert McIntosh, gamekeeper and gillie at Dalguise, 1879; 228; 1 item 12.1 x 16.4 cm.
    Catalog number: 449
  - Horse and cart, with men, undated; 229; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Catalog number: 450
  - Horse, cart, and dog, with woodman, undated; 230; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Catalog number: 451
  - Horse, cart, and dog, without woodman, undated; 231; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Catalog number: 452
  - Back view of a laden cart, undated; 232; 1 item 10.8 x 15.3 cm.
    Title supplied by catalog. No inscription.
    Catalog number: 503
  - Horses, at a sale or show, undated; 233; 1 item 5.6 x 8.5 cm.
    Cataloger supplied title. No inscription. Printed on SELO paper.
    Catalog number: 453
  - Horses, at a sale or show, undated; 234; 1 item 5.6 x 8.5 cm.
  - Horses, at a sale or show; man looking into camera, foreground right, undated; 235; 1 item 5.6 x 8.5 cm.
  - Horse and yearling, and two young boys; at a show or sale, undated; 236; 1 item 5.6 x 8.5 cm.
  - Pony with docked tail, facing right, held by young boy with stick; at a show or sale, undated; 237; 1 item 5.6 x 8.5 cm.
  - Pony and woodman's cart, with collie, on a hillside, undated; 238; 1 item 5.8 x 8.5 cm.
  - Pony with docked tail, wearing number on bridle, held by boy with stick; at a show or sale, undated; 239; 1 item 5.8 x 8.6 cm.
  - Boy feeding a piglet from a bottle, undated; 240; 1 item 16.3 x 12.0 cm.
    Catalog number: 454
  - White rabbit in a wire run; Tommy?, circa 1879; 241; 1 item 8.7 x 12.2 cm.